{ "questions" : [
{
"question":"What do you call a boomerang that won't come back?",
"answer":"A stick."
},
{
"question":"How is a lawyer different from a hooker?",
"answer":"There are some things a hooker just won't do."
},
{
"question":"How many divorced men does it take to screw in a light bulb?",
"answer":"None, the sockets go with the house."
},
{
"question":"What do you call a man with a car on his head?",
"answer":"Jack"
},
{
"question":"What's Black and Brown and looks good on a lawyer?",
"answer":"A Doberman."
},
{
"question":"What's the difference between a bad golfer and a bad skydiver?",
"answer":"A bad golfer goes, WHACK! Damn. A bad skydiver goes, Damn. WHACK!"
},{
"question":"What do you call a lawyer skydiving?",
"answer":"A skeet."
},{
"question":"Which sexual position produces the ugliest children?",
"answer":"Ask your mother."
},{
"question":"How do you embarrass an archeologist?",
"answer":"Give him a used tampon and ask him which period it came from."
},{
"question":"What did the cannibal do after he dumped his girlfriend?",
"answer":"Wiped his ass."
},{
"question":"How can you tell if you're at a bulimic bachelor party?",
"answer":"The cake jumps out of the girl."
},{
"question":"What do you call a prostitute with a runny nose?",
"answer":"Full."
},{
"question":"How do you circumcise a hillbilly?",
"answer":"Kick his sister in the jaw."
},{
"question":"What's the difference between Courtney Love & Eric Lindross?",
"answer":"Eric takes a shower after 3 periods"
},{
"question":"Why doesn't Mexico have an Olympic team?",
"answer":"Because everybody who can run, jump and swim are already in the U.S."
},{
"question":"What's the difference between a bitch and a whore?",
"answer":"A whore sleeps with everybody at the party, and a bitch sleeps with everybody at the party except you."
},{
"question":"What are three words you dread the most while making love?",
"answer":"Honey, I'm home."
},{
"question":"Why don't they teach driver's education and sex education on the same day in Iraq?",
"answer":"They don't want to wear out the camel."
},{
"question":"What's the difference between a Catholic wife and a Jewish wife?",
"answer":"A Catholic wife has real orgasms and fake jewelry."
},{
"question":"What's the difference between getting a divorce and getting circumcised?",
"answer":"When you get a divorce, you get rid of the whole prick!"
},{
"question":"What's the difference between a G-Spot and a golf ball?",
"answer":"A guy will actually search for a golf ball."
},{
"question":"What did One gay sperm say to another?",
"answer":"How do we find an egg in all of this crap?"
},{
"question":"What did the elephant say to the naked man?",
"answer":"It's cute but can you pick up peanuts with it?"
},{
"question":"What has seventy-five balls and screws old ladies?",
"answer":"Bingo!"
},{
"question":"What's the definition of a Yankee?",
"answer":"Same thing as a 'quickie', only you do it yourself."
},{
"question":"How does every ethnic joke start?",
"answer":"By looking over your shoulder."
},{
"question":"Which of the following doesn't belong: wife, meat, eggs, blow job?",
"answer":"The blow job. You can beat your wife, your eggs, or your meat; but you just can't beat a blow job."
},{
"question":"How many perverts does it take to put in a light bulb?",
"answer":"Just one, but it takes the entire emergency room to get it out!"
},{
"question":"What did the Indian say to the white woman when she tied his penis in a knot?",
"answer":"'How Come?'"
},{
"question":"What is the difference between a genealogist and a gynecologist?",
"answer":"A genealogist looks up your family tree. A gynecologist looks up your family bush."
},{
"question":"Why are cowgirls bowlegged?",
"answer":"Cowboys like to eat with their hats on."
},{
"question":"What's the definition of a teenager?",
"answer":"God's punishment for enjoying sex."
},{
"question":"Did you hear the slogan for the the new 'Stealth Condom?'",
"answer":"'They'll never see you coming.'"
},{
"question":"How is a woman like a road?",
"answer":"Both have manholes."
},{
"question":"What's the definition of a vagina?",
"answer":"The box a penis comes in."
},{
"question":"What do you call a truckload of vibrators?",
"answer":"Toys for Twats."
},{
"question":"What do you call kinky sex with chocolate?",
"answer":"S&M&M."
},{
"question":"What",
"answer":"Ans"
}


]}